One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash through, and face the challenge!
These are our hard knock days.
Can't quench our thirst with a peaceful, everyday life.
Here we go - don't ever run away!
Let's go on living as the mighty winds take us!
We've still got so far to go.
Gotta keep going through the hard knock days.
Let's do it again, yes, baby. How many times
do I have to stand back up to make my dream come true?
Feels like the strength of my resolve
is put to the test everyday.
Hey, let's go!
I don't want to make excuses and settle for being mediocre.
We leapt into a crazy, lawless world.
As I struggled for a foothold, reality caught me off guard.
Even if it beats me, hits me, knocks me down again,
Oh!
Only when we get back on our feet and look forward,
will we have the last laugh, be the winners!
We gotta go down this glory road, till we reach our goal!
Fight, shake it off, act strong!
These are our hard knock days.
There's no such thing as a safe choice.
Here we go - we'll always be the strongest!
Let's keep moving - never mind the consequences.
Let's put our wishes all together,
and keep on going through the hard knock days.
White Town
Port Town Spider Miles
Waste Processing Plant
Boy from the White Town
Trafalgar Law
(Age 10)
Throw him out!
Hey, hey, Law!
It's been a week already.
Don't you wanna run away?
You've been getting beaten by Corazón ever since you came here.
Kids and adults alike run away.
That's why we have only the strongest.
How much longer will a useless brat like you last?
No matter what happens, don't forget the blood law.
The Family will fall apart if a member defies a commander's authority.
I once laughed at Pica-sama
and almost died from the torture.
It doesn't scare me.
I've seen hell itself.
Donquixote Pirates
Captain
Donquixote Doflamingo
You're free to say what you want...
But Corazón is my precious younger brother of my own blood.
If anyone so much as nicks him, I'll...
put them to death!
Look at his skin!
The White Lead Disease!
It's agonizing pain if you're infected!
What?! It's contagious?! That's gross!
Get out of here now-dasuyan!
Giolla, don't treat mere rumors as fact.
Shame on you.
Look, Buffalo believed you.
The White Lead Disease is a poison.
It's not contagious.
But stay away from me just in case-dasuyan!
I don't wanna catch that disease-dasuyan!
Hey.
Are there any other survivors from the White Town, Flevance?
I don't know.
It took everything I had just to escape.
How did you get out?
I crossed the border by hiding under a pile of dead bodies.
Hey! I'm eating!
Why so much malice?
I don't believe in anything anymore.
I'm not afraid of death.
Corazón!
Don't push your luck!
I'll get my revenge on you at any cost!
Hey, are you stupid?
Weren't you listening?!
They'll torture you if you do that!
Impalement!
Don't mess with pirates!
Children are idiots. They think crying and saying sorry will make things better!
Port Town Rakesh
Hey, what kind of place is the White Town, where that kid was from?
It was a country called Flevance.
The White Town was a nickname for it.
Flevance?
Yeah.
All of its citizens were rich, and the towns were all white, from the soil to the plants...
Like winter in a fairy tale.
I heard the country's beauty was out of this world.
One day, they discovered White Lead, a type of lead, underground...
And found out that was the source of the fantastic scenery.
They made utensils, paint, sweeteners, cosmetics, and even weapons out of White Lead.
People all over the world wanted to buy their high-quality White Lead goods...
And it became Flevance's flagship industry.
The cunning World Government went into the transport business to ship that merchandise.
White Lead made people a fortune.
Law, for this kind of surgery, you use that blood vessel.
Oh really?
Big brother! Let's go to the festival!
Yeah. Why don't you three go?
All right, but just for half an hour.
We have so many patients to take care of.
Yeah!
Law! Let's go! To the festival!
The White Town was the place everyone longed for.
Oh, I wanna go there!
"G", for longed!
But it's gone now.
What?
About a century ago, when the White Lead industry was established...
The World Government performed a geological survey in the country...
And so they already knew the truth.
The truth?
It was poison.
What?
Poison that wasn't harmful unless you dig it up.
But if you handle it, it'll decay your body.
What?!
Knowing this, but blinded by the easy fortune to be had,
the Government and the royalty of that country kept it secret.
Their citizens kept mining it, knowing nothing.
But that means they would die.
Yeah.
The terrible part was it only contained traces of poison.
Say that the Lead keeps building up in a young person's body.
When they have a child, they will actually have a shorter life expectancy.
Then when the kid grows up and has their own child...
That child's life expectancy is even shorter.
Age
Life Expectancy
The negative effect
on future generations
Age 70
Age 50
Age 30
No more
descendants
Life expectancy grew shorter, generation by generation,
until eventually a generation doomed to die before adulthood, just like Law, was born.
When the world finally realized that White Lead was poisonous...
It was too late.
At some point, people started to collapse one after another.
Grandparents, parents, and then children.
Because of the differences in their life expectancies, all generations fell ill around the same time.
Their skin and hair rapidly whitened.
People died one after another, their entire bodies racked with pain.
No doctor could stop it.
Then, all the people in his country died?!
Poor them...
The real tragedy began after that.
Huh?
Seeing the people in the White Town all dying with the same symptoms,
people in neighboring countries thought White Lead Disease was contagious.
White Town
So they formed a blockade around the country and took quarantine measures against the White Town.
The royal family got help from the Government and escaped the country at an early stage.
They abandoned their subjects.
People from the White Town who were looking to be treated and immigrate to other countries
were feared like wild beasts escaping from their cage, and they were shot dead.
They swept the whole situation under the rug.
Dammit!
The suffering the disease caused was just somebody else's problem.
It was a natural human reaction.
But Flevance couldn't keep quiet.
Ironically, they had tons of lead bullets.
Eventually, a war broke out.
Other countries justified their actions as self defense, so they showed no mercy.
I'm sure you can imagine the rest.
Law-kun!
Come, you must leave with us.
There are gentle soldiers who told us they will let only the children escape!
Law!
We'll be safe!
Sister! My little sister is dying!
I can't go now!
Lammy-chan?!
I see...
Then, let's ask them to get you on board the next refugee ship!
I'll come back to pick you up!
Law! Aren't you coming?!
Let's escape together!
I'm sure they'll save Lammy later, too!
Both my mom and dad are dead!
But they told me to live!
So I'm gonna live no matter what!
Listen, Law-kun.
There is always hope.
A merciful helping hand will...
always reach out to you, like this.
Doctor, help!
Doctor!
It's impossible! I can't go there!
We don't have enough doctors!
Same for blood and everything!
There must be a way to clear away White Lead from bodies!
And it's not contagious!
Why doesn't the Government report that?!
Big brother, my body hurts.
My skin's getting whiter and whiter...
Hang on for a little more.
Our father is the greatest doctor in the country.
He'll cure you!
Why is it so noisy outside?
There's a festival!
Flevance is always booming.
Get well soon and let's go to a festival together again!
Uh-huh!
Lammy, stay in here for a few minutes.
Uh-huh...
Two infected people have been terminated!
Law!
Law! Let's go! To the festival!
Mother!
Father!
Listen, Law-kun.
There is always hope.
A merciful helping hand will...
always reach out to you, like this.
Sister!
Everybody!
Let's escape together!
So I'm gonna live no matter what!
The hospital...!
Lammy!
Flevance, the White Town, perished.
In the end, it was done by humans.
If a ten-year-old kid went through such an ordeal...
There's no way it wouldn't screw up his personality.
There he is! Corazón!
My parents, my sister, and everyone from the church are all dead...
Yet that idiot is alive! It's not fair!
They won't know if I keep quiet.
Nobody will notice...
If a scumbag goes missing!
Damn! I was seen!
He... b-broke the... blood law!
He deserves impalement-dasuyan!
I must inform the young master-dasuyan!
They're a family of Celestial Dragons!
Kill them!
They're former Celestial Dragons.
The Navy won't interfere, even if we kill them.
The admirals won't come, either!
I'm so glad I got a chance for revenge!
I thought I'd have to bear it silently all my life!
Break all their bones with a hammer!
Shoot them with a thousand arrows!
No! Don't let them die so easily!
Keep them alive and let them suffer long and well!
Listen, you fiends!
My sons were only five and two years old...
And all they did was cut across the path of the Celestial Dragons...
For something so small...
They were killed!
My enslaved daughter came home looking like she'd been through hell,
and she killed herself, without a word, three days later!
I was once your slave! And my eyes...
Because of you... Because of you...
Give me back my wife!
You guys don't give a damn about our lives!
Because of the Heavenly Tribute we pay to you fools,
my country was destroyed by famine!
Have you ever been hungry?!
Everyone became skin and bones, and died!
So you guys are gods, huh?!
You're different from humans, right?
Then, I bet this won't kill you!
Doffy!
Brother!
Dammit!
H-How dare you...
Treat us humans worse than worms!
Do you know what it's like to be in pain, grief, agony?!
Well, Celestial Dragons?!
What is it?
The Holy Land Mariejoa, 33 years ago
Are you insane, Saint Homing?!
You, of all people?!
You're saying you renounce your status as a god and reduce yourself to a mere human?!
World Noble (Celestial Dragon)
Saint Donquixote Homing
I am human, and I have always been.
Do you imply we are too?!
That's sacrilege!
Who do you think we Celestial Dragons are?!
Traitor! You have always been heretical!
He's right, traitor!
So savage!
Get out of Mariejoa now!
We cannot take you farther than here.
We're at the north end.
A non-member nation of the World Government.
Some assets and an adequate house are ready for you there.
Thank you. That's all we need.
Now, I'll collect your Celestial Dragon ID chips.
Let's live a humble life here, all four of us as a family.
Father! Where are the slaves?
If there aren't any, let's go buy some.
Doffy. Rosinante.
We have to teach you from scratch.
Doffy, we are going to live as humans from now on.
Humans?
We'll lead a life far richer than the life in Mariejoa.
Not "rich" in the sense that we'll have money and possessions.
I mean spiritually.
Hey!
Why don't you kneel before us?!
You fools are disrespectful!
You just cut across in front of me, didn't you?
Somebody, fetch me a pistol!
Who do you think I am?!
Where are the Celestial Dragons?!
Find them!
Hang them up!
Father, why don't they kneel before us?
They're not in here! They must've run!
Find them! They can't have gone far!
Don't kill them! Keep them alive, and let them suffer!
Yeah!
We will take revenge on that family for centuries of injustice!
Doffy!
Father! Why do they come after us?!
We should be thankful to be out of the rain here at least.
People around here haven't heard about us yet.
How can I live in such a filthy place?!
There are bugs inside the house! The smell here makes me sick!
Find the family!
They should still be around here!
Kill them as soon as you find them!
We must run! Now!
I never imagined it would turn out this bad.
I was too optimistic. Please! I'll do anything!
Would you please let us go back to Mariejoa? At least take back my wife and children!
If we stay here, we'll be killed!
That was your own choosing.
You cannot take back what you gave up.
Don't ever call me again!
You're no more than a human!
You bread thieves!
Father! For the first time in my life...
I feel pain!
Father!
For the first time in my life, I'm hungry!
Eat fast, Rosy!
Somebody's gonna come!
Mother, we brought you some food.
Doffy. Rosy.
Mother!
I'm sorry... I don't...
feel very well...
Father...
Mother is dead!
We got them!
Please, you can have me, but let my children go!
Please! I'm begging you!
Father!
Damn you!
Look at what you've done!
Young master, we've caught Law!
Looks like he was thinking of escaping.
Dammit! Let go of me!
He was already at the port-in.
They'll start torturing him for stabbing Cora-san-dasuyan!
I feel so sorry for Law...
Corazón!
Damn! He didn't die!
I'm gonna get done in for nothing?!
I shut Buffalo's mouth by buying him an ice cream...
But that guy told him himself!
I'm sure the blade went through his body!
How can he act like he's fine?!
Law...
I called you in for just one thing.
I've decided to make you an official member of the Donquixote Family.
The Family-in!
Because you went through such a horrible experience,
you developed that incomparable, hateful look in your eyes.
You have what it takes.
He sees potential in your future!
The young master is a visionary.
Doesn't he know what I did to Corazón yet?
Why? He can tell him in writing.
What is he up to?
Even if he sees potential in me, I'll die in three years anyway!
That depends on your luck!
Luck?
We deal mainly in the black market.
We handle Devil Fruits, as well.
Some Devil Fruits give powers that defy common sense.
There might be a Fruit that could cure your disease.
Devil Fruits?
If you're lucky,
your life could be saved by a Devil Fruit we come across in the three years you have left.
I will train you to become my right-hand man ten years from now.
What's wrong?
An
enemy
You were attacked?
Did you take care of him?
I got
rid of
him
That's good, then. Now go have your wounds treated.
Did he just... cover up for me?
What is he playing at?!
We'll keep moving our base of operations toward Reverse Mountain in the southeast...
and expand our business.
2 years later
We told you our real names!
So what? I'm not interested!
You're so uncool! No fun!
Fun or not, I'll die anyway.
You have quite a lot of white parts now.
I don't know if I'll survive another year.
I may die sooner than I calculated.
That aside, if you have a real name, tell us-dasuyan!
Or I'll tell the young master you stabbed Cora-san two years ago!
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
I'm supposed to keep that name secret.
But since I don't go by a code name like you two, it doesn't really matter.
"D." is a secret name, and "Water" is taboo...
For generations, my family-
What a boring name.
Yeah-dasuyan.
You're the ones who kept nagging me about it!
Hey, let go of me!
What the... Corazón! What do you want?! Hey!
Oh, he's gonna get beaten again.
Cora-san looked scarier than usual.
What do you want, Corazón?! Do you wanna fight?!
Was that true, what you just said?
Eh?
Huh? What? Who's there?!
The secret name "D."...
If it's true, you need to get out of here.
Get away from Doffy!
Law! You have to stay far away from him!